Foster Gunnison, Jr. Papers
© 2006 University of Connecticut
- Series II: Institute for Social Ethics Archive, undated, 1956-1999
  - Subseries A: Related to Homophile Movement, 1956-1999
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," 900 Los Angeles, CA, 1970-1971 (Box 17:, Folder 203)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," 900 Los Angeles, CA, 1970-1971 (Box 17:, Folder 204)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," 900 Los Angeles, CA, 1970-1971 (Box 17:, Folder 205)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," 930 Santa Barbara, CA, 1971 (Box 17:, Folder 206)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," 941 San Francisco, 1970-1971 (Box 17:, Folder 207)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," 943 Gay Student Union, 1971 (Box 17:, Folder 208)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," 945 and 946 CA, 1971 (Box 17:, Folder 209)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," 947 Berkeley, CA, 1971 (Box 17:, Folder 210)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," 981 Seattle, WA, 1970-1971 (Box 17:, Folder 211)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," Belgium, 1970-1971 (Box 17:, Folder 212)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," Canada, 1970-1971 (Box 17:, Folder 213)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," England, 1970-1972 (Box 17:, Folder 214)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," European, 1971 (Box 17:, Folder 215)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," Finland, 1971 (Box 17:, Folder 216)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," Holland, 1970-1971 (Box 17:, Folder 217)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," Switzerland, 1970-1971 (Box 17:, Folder 218)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," Sweden, 1971 (Box 17:, Folder 219)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," Directory Listings, 1971-1972 (Box 17:, Folder 220)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, "Gunnison's Guide," Directory Listings, undated (Box 17:, Folder 221)
    - Institute of Social Ethics, Office Files, 1966-1993 (Box 17:, Folder 222)
    - Institute for the Study of American Religion, 1974-1975 (Box 17:, Folder 223)
    - Institute for the Study of Human Resources, 1968-1978 (Box 17:, Folder 224)
    - International Gay and Lesbian Archives, Board of Trustees Reports, 1981-1986 (Box 18:, Folder 225)
    - International Gay and Lesbian Archives, Board of Trustees Reports, 1986-1993 (Box 18:, Folder 226)
    - International Gay and Lesbian Archives, Calendars, 1981-1988 (Box 18:, Folder 227)
    - International Gay and Lesbian Archives, Correspondence with Gunnison, 1982-1993 (Box 18:, Folder 228)
    - International Gay and Lesbian Archives, Informational Pamphlets, 1985-1993 (Box 18:, Folder 229)
    - International Gay and Lesbian Archives, Mailings, 1980-1990 (Box 18:, Folder 230)
    - International Gay Youth Information Pool, 1985-1986 (Box 18:, Folder 231)
    - Janus/Homosexual Law Reform Society, Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 18:, Folder 232)
    - Janus/Homosexual Law Reform Society, Mailings and Releases, 1966-1968 (Box 18:, Folder 233)
    - Janus/Homosexual Law Reform Society, Publications, 1965-1968 (Box 18:, Folder 234)
    - Kalos Society, Keith Brown Collection, 1968-1970 (Box 18:, Folder 235)
    - Kalos Society, Correspondence, 1967-1972, 1982 (Box 18:, Folder 236)
    - Kalos Society, Fliers and Announcements, 1969-1971 (Box 18:, Folder 237)
    - Kalos Society, Informational Literature, 1970-1973 (Box 18:, Folder 238)
    - Kalos Society, Membership Mailings, 1970-1971 (Box 19:, Folder 239)
    - Kalos Society, Office Files, 1968-1971 (Box 19:, Folder 240)
    - Kalos Society, Official Letters and Releases, 1970-1971 (Box 19:, Folder 241)
    - Kalos Society, Programs, 1968-1970 (Box 19:, Folder 242)
    - Lambda, Inc., Fliers, 1972 (Box 19:, Folder 243)
    - Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, Inc., 1984-1989 (Box 19:, Folder 244)
    - Lavderdale Beach Hotel, 1977 (Box 19:, Folder 245)
    - Le-Hi-Ho, 1970 (Box 19:, Folder 246)
    - Lesbian/Gay Liberation March, 1984 (Box 19:, Folder 247)
    - March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1979, 1986-1987 (Box 19:, Folder 248)
    - Massachusetts Gay Political Caucus, 1982-1988 (Box 19:, Folder 249)
    - Mattachine Society, Inc., Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 19:, Folder 250)
    - Mattachine Society, Inc., Fliers, Announcements and Mailings, 1952-1967 (Box 19:, Folder 251)
    - Mattachine Society, Inc., Fliers, Announcements and Mailings, 1965-1967 (Box 19:, Folder 252)
    - Mattachine Society of Florida, Office Files, 1965-1968 (Box 19:, Folder 253)
    - Mattachine Midwest, Correspondence to/from Gunnison, 1965-1968 (Box 20:, Folder 254)
    - Mattachine Midwest, Correspondence to/from Gunnison, 1968 May - December (Box 20:, Folder 255)
    - Mattachine Midwest, Fliers, Announcements and Mailings, 1965-1970 (Box 20:, Folder 256)
    - Mattachine Society of New York, Correspondence, 1966-1978 (Box 20:, Folder 257)
    - Mattachine Society of New York, Financial Statements, 1965-1971 (Box 20:, Folder 258)
    - Mattachine Society of New York, Fliers and Announcements, 1965 (Box 20:, Folder 259)
    - Mattachine Society of New York, Fliers and Announcements, 1966 January - August (Box 20:, Folder 260)
    - Mattachine Society of New York, Fliers and Announcements, 1966 September - 1967 December (Box 20:, Folder 261)
    - Mattachine Society of New York, Fliers and Announcements, 1968 (Box 20:, Folder 262)
    - Mattachine Society of New York, Fliers and Announcements, 1969 (Box 21:, Folder 263)
    - Mattachine Society of New York, Fliers and Announcements, 1970 (Box 21:, Folder 264)
    - Mattachine Society of New York, Fliers and Announcements, 1971-1972 (Box 21:, Folder 265)
    - Mattachine Society of New York, Fliers and Announcements, 1973-1977 (Box 21:, Folder 266)
    - Mattachine Society of New York, "Man-To-Man" Scurvies, undated (Box 21:, Folder 267)
    - Mattachine Society of Niagra Frontier, 1972-1975 (Box 21:, Folder 268)
    - Mattachine Society of Philadelphia, 1965-1966 (Box 21:, Folder 269)
    - Mattachine Society of Washington, Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 21:, Folder 270)
    - Mattachine Society of Washington, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 21:, Folder 271)
    - Mattachine Society of Washington, Correspondence, 1968 January - May (Box 21:, Folder 272)
    - Mattachine Society of Washington, Correspondence, 1968 January - 1972 November (Box 21:, Folder 273)
    - Mattachine Society of Washington, Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 21:, Folder 274)
    - Mattachine Society of Washington, Fliers, Announcements and Mailings, 1962-1964 (Box 21:, Folder 275)
    - Mattachine Society of Washington, Fliers, Announcements and Mailings, 1965 (Box 22:, Folder 276)
    - Mattachine Society of Washington, Fliers, Announcements and Mailings, 1966 (Box 22:, Folder 277)
    - Mattachine Society of Washington, Fliers, Announcements and Mailings, 1967 (Box 22:, Folder 278)
    - Mattachine Society of Washington, Fliers, Announcements and Mailings, 1968 (Box 22:, Folder 279)
    - Mattachine Society of Washington, Fliers, Announcements and Mailings, 1970-1972 (Box 22:, Folder 280)
    - Mattachine Society of Washington, Gunnison Related Items, 1966-1967 (Box 22:, Folder 281)
    - Metropolitan Community Church, Hartford, 1974-1979 (Box 22:, Folder 282)
    - Metropolitan Community Church, Los Angeles, 1970-1977 (Box 22:, Folder 283)
    - Metropolitan Community Church, New York, 1970-1978 (Box 22:, Folder 284)
    - Metropolitan Community Church, New Haven and Detroit, 1971-1972 (Box 22:, Folder 285)
    - Metropolitan Community Church, Washington D.C., 1970-1976 (Box 22:, Folder 286)
    - Midwestern Regional Conference of Homophile Organizations, 1967-1968 (Box 23:, Folder 287)
    - National Coalition of Gay Organizations, 1972 (Box 23:, Folder 288)
    - National Council of Churches, 1966 (Box 23:, Folder 289)
    - National Gay Task Force, Fliers, Announcements and Mailings, 1973-1976 (Box 23:, Folder 290)
    - National Gay Task Force, Fliers, Announcements and Mailings, 1977 (Box 23:, Folder 291)
    - National Gay Task Force, Fliers, Announcements and Mailings, 1978 (Box 23:, Folder 292)
    - National Gay Task Force, Fliers, Announcements and Mailings, 1979-1982 (Box 23:, Folder 293)
    - National League for Social Understanding, Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 23:, Folder 294)
    - National League for Social Understanding, Fliers and Announcements, 1961-1968 (Box 23:, Folder 295)
    - National Legal Defense Fund, Correspondence and Pamphlets, 1967-1968 (Box 23:, Folder 296)
    - National Lesbian/Gay Health Foundation, 1985-1989 (Box 23:, Folder 297)
    - National Organization of Gay and Lesbian Scientists, 1978-1988 (Box 23:, Folder 298)
    - National Sex Forum, 1970-1984 (Box 23:, Folder 299)
    - New Jersey Gay Coalition, 1972 (Box 24:, Folder 300)
    - New Jersey League for Social Action, 1966 (Box 24:, Folder 301)
    - New York Council of Friends of ONE, 1966-1967 (Box 24:, Folder 302)
    - New York Council of Friends of ONE, 1968 (Box 24:, Folder 303)
    - New York Council of Friends of ONE, 1966-1967 (Box 24:, Folder 304)
    - New York Council of Friends of ONE, 1968-1973 (Box 24:, Folder 305)
    - New York Council of Friends of ONE, 1967-1969 (Box 24:, Folder 306)
    - New York Council of Friends of ONE, 1966-1967 (Box 24:, Folder 307)
    - Ohio Mattachine, Inc., 1969 (Box 24:, Folder 308)
    - ONE, Annual Reports and Minutes, 1958-1964 (Box 24:, Folder 309)
    - ONE, Annual Reports and Minutes, 1966-1985 (Box 24:, Folder 310)
    - ONE, Correspondence to/from Gunnison, 1966-1967 (Box 25:, Folder 311)
    - ONE, Correspondence to/from Gunnison, 1968-1969 (Box 25:, Folder 312)
    - ONE, Fliers, Announcements, 1955-1965 (Box 25:, Folder 313)
    - ONE, Fliers, Announcements, Mailings, 1966 (Box 25:, Folder 314)
    - ONE, Fliers, Announcements, Mailings, 1967-1968 (Box 25:, Folder 315)
    - ONE, Fliers, Announcements, Mailings, 1969-1975 (Box 25:, Folder 316)
    - ONE, Fliers, Announcements, Mailings, 1976-1993 (Box 25:, Folder 317)
    - ONE, Historical File and Gunnison's Notes, 1953, 1967 (Box 25:, Folder 318)
    - ONE, Office Files, 1955-1965 (Box 25:, Folder 319)
    - ONE, Book Service, 1959-1968 (Box 25:, Folder 320)
    - ONE of Chicago, Fliers, Announcements, Mailings, 1966-1967 (Box 25:, Folder 321)
    - ONE of Chicago, Fliers, Announcements, Mailings, 1968-1971 (Box 25:, Folder 322)
    - ONE of Chicago, Fliers, Announcements, Mailings, 1972-1973 (Box 26:, Folder 323)
    - ONE of Chicago, Fliers, Announcements, Mailings, 1974-1979 (Box 26:, Folder 324)
    - ONE of Detroit, 1971-1972 (Box 26:, Folder 325)
    - Oscar Wilde Memorial Bookshop, Catalogues, 1967-1976 (Box 26:, Folder 326)
    - Oscar Wilde Memorial Bookshop, Catalogues, 1977-1993 (Box 26:, Folder 327)
    - Oscar Wilde Memorial Bookshop, Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 26:, Folder 328)
    - Pacific Center, 1976 (Box 26:, Folder 329)
    - People's Party, 1972 (Box 26:, Folder 330)
    - Phoenix Society for Individual Freedom, Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 26:, Folder 331)
    - Phoenix Society for Individual Freedom, Fliers and Announcements, 1966-1968 (Box 26:, Folder 332)
    - PRIDE, Correspondence to/from Gunnison, 1967-1968 (Box 26:, Folder 333)
    - PRIDE, Mailings, Fliers, Announcements, 1966-1968 (Box 26:, Folder 334)
    - PRO Toledo/Personal Rights Organizations of Toledo, 1969-1972 (Box 26:, Folder 335)
    - Project "H", Correspondence to/from Gunnison, 1965-1966 (Box 27:, Folder 336)
    - Project "H", Correspondence to/from Gunnison, 1966-1969 (Box 27:, Folder 337)
    - Project "H", Fliers, Announcements, Mailings, 1967-1979 (Box 27:, Folder 338)
    - Project "H", Historical Information, 1964-1971 (Box 27:, Folder 339)
    - Promethan Society of Houston, 1968 (Box 27:, Folder 340)
    - Prosperos, Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 27:, Folder 341)
    - Prosperos, Fliers, Announcements, Mailings, 1969-1976 (Box 27:, Folder 342)
    - Pursuit, Correspondence, Jim Kepner to/from Gunnison, 1966-1967 (Box 27:, Folder 343)
    - Pursuit, Correspondence, Jim Kepner to/from Gunnison, 1967-1968 (Box 27:, Folder 344)
    - Pursuit, Fliers, Announcements, Mailings, 1966-1967 (Box 27:, Folder 345)
    - Queens Quarterly, 1969-1973 (Box 27:, Folder 346)
    - Red Butterfly, 1970 (Box 27:, Folder 347)
    - The Saint, 1986-1987 (Box 27:, Folder 348)
    - SAME/John Gale, 1967 (Box 27:, Folder 349)
    - San Francisco Homophile League, Correspondence to/from Gunnison, 1967-1968 (Box 28:, Folder 350)
    - San Francisco Homophile League, Correspondence from Others, 1967 (Box 28:, Folder 351)
    - San Francisco Homophile League, Mailings, 1967-1968 (Box 28:, Folder 352)
    - San Francisco Homophile League, Official Documents, 1967 (Box 28:, Folder 353)
    - SDA Kinship, 1987-1988 (Box 28:, Folder 354)
    - Seattle Gay Alliance, 1971-1973 (Box 28:, Folder 355)
    - Siecus, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 28:, Folder 356)
    - Siecus, Mailings, 1967-1972 (Box 28:, Folder 357)
    - Society of Annibis, 1970 (Box 28:, Folder 358)
    - Society for Individual Rights, Ohio, Announcements and Correspondence, undated, 1970 (Box 28:, Folder 359)
    - Society for Individual Rights, San Francisco Announcements, 1965-1974 (Box 28:, Folder 360)
    - Society for Individual Rights, San Francisco Announcements, 1965-1972 (Box 28:, Folder 361)
    - Society for Individual Rights, San Francisco, Brochures and Handouts, 1965-1968 (Box 28:, Folder 362)
    - Society for Individual Rights, San Francisco, Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 29:, Folder 363)
    - Society for Individual Rights, San Francisco, Incorporation, Office File, 1964-1967 (Box 29:, Folder 364)
    - Society for Individual Rights, San Francisco, Membership Cards, 1965-1972 (Box 29:, Folder 365)
    - Society for Individual Rights, San Francisco, News clippings, 1966, 1968 (Box 29:, Folder 366)
    - Society for Individual Rights, San Francisco, Playbooks, 1965-1968 (Box 29:, Folder 367)
    - Society for Individual Rights, San Francisco, Publication, 1967 (Box 29:, Folder 368)
    - Society for Individual Rights, San Francisco, Publication, 1968 (Box 29:, Folder 369)
    - Society for Individual Rights, San Francisco, Publication, 1966 (Box 29:, Folder 370)
    - Society for Individual Rights, San Francisco, Office Files, 1965-1967, 1970 (Box 30:, Folder 371)
    - Society for Individual Rights, San Francisco, Seminars and Schedules, 1966-1969 (Box 30:, Folder 372)
    - Student Homophile League, Columbia University, Bulletins, 1966-1967 (Box 30:, Folder 373)
    - Student Homophile League, Columbia University, Bulletins, 1967-1969 (Box 30:, Folder 374)
    - Student Homophile League, Columbia University, Fliers, 1967-1970 (Box 30:, Folder 375)
    - Student Homophile League, Columbia University, Office Files, 1966-1969 (Box 30:, Folder 376)
    - Student Homophile League, Cornell University, 1968-1970 (Box 30:, Folder 377)
    - Student Homophile League, Announcements and Brochures, Hartford, 1967 (Box 30:, Folder 378)
    - Student Homophile League, Hartford, Announcements, 1967-1968, 1975 (Box 31:, Folder 379)
    - Student Homophile League, Harvard-Radcliffe/MIT, 1970-1972 (Box 31:, Folder 380)
    - Student Homophile League, New York University, 1970-1972 (Box 31:, Folder 381)
    - Student Homophile League, Homophiles of Penn State, 1971-1972 (Box 31:, Folder 382)
    - Student Homophile League, Rutgers University, 1971-1973 (Box 31:, Folder 383)
    - Student Homophile League, York University, 1971-1972 (Box 31:, Folder 384)
    - Students and Youth Coalition for People's Peace, Announcements, 1971 (Box 31:, Folder 385)
    - Syracuse Gay Freedom League, Announcements, 1972-1973 (Box 31:, Folder 386)
    - The Swedish Union for Sexual Equality, Announcements, 1971-1973 (Box 31:, Folder 387)
    - Tangents, Announcements and Brochures, 1965-1968 (Box 31:, Folder 388)
    - Tangents, Book Lists, 1966-1968 (Box 31:, Folder 389)
    - Tangents,Committee to Fight Exclusion, 1966-1970 (Box 31:, Folder 390)
    - Tangents, Correspondence Relating to Tangent Orders, 1967-1968 (Box 31:, Folder 391)
    - Tangents, Newsletters and Highlights, 1966-1968 (Box 31:, Folder 392)
    - Tavern Guild of San Francisco, Announcements, Bulletins, Newsletters, 1966-1967 (Box 31:, Folder 393)
    - Tidewater Homophile League, 1967 (Box 31:, Folder 394)
    - United Church of Christ, 1969 (Box 31:, Folder 395)
    - Vanguard Publications, Announcements and Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 32:, Folder 396)
    - Vector, 1973 (Box 32:, Folder 397)
    - West Side Discussion Group, Announcements, 1967-1968, 1973-1976 (Box 32:, Folder 398)
    - West Side Discussion Group, Constitution and Brochures, 1967-1968, 1973 (Box 32:, Folder 399)
    - West Side Discussion Group, Correspondence, 1967-1973 (Box 32:, Folder 400)
    - Western Regional Conference of Homophile Organizations, 1967 (Box 32:, Folder 401)
    - Subject Files
    - Adult books and magazines - catalogs, 1970-1985 (Box 37:, Folder 444)
    - Adult books and magazines - subscription mailers>, 1968-1970 (Box 37:, Folder 445)
    - Adult films - catalogs, mailers, 1971-1985, 1993 (Box 37:, Folder 446)
    - Adult books and magazines, Trojan Book Service - correspondence, news releases, reviews, 1966-1967 (Box 37:, Folder 446)
    - Adult books and magazines, Trojan Book Service - mailers, catalogs, 1966-1970 (Box 37:, Folder 447)
    - Adult toys - catalogs, mailers, 1968-1973 (Box 37:, Folder 465)
    - AIDS, 1983-1986 (Box 32:, Folder 402)
    - AIDS, 1987-1988 (Box 32:, Folder 403)
    - AIDS, 1968 (Box 32:, Folder 404)
    - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation, Cases and Mailings, 1963-1966 (Box 32:, Folder 405)
    - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation, Cases and Mailings, 1967 (Box 33:, Folder 406)
    - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation, Cases and Mailings, 1968-1969 (Box 33:, Folder 407)
    - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation, Cases and Mailings, 1970-1978 (Box 33:, Folder 408)
    - Bibliographies of Gay Materials, 1967-1975 (Box 33:, Folder 409)
    - Bibliographies of Gay Materials, 1977 (Box 33:, Folder 410)
    - Book and Journal Announcements, 1967-1973 (Box 33:, Folder 411)
    - Book and Journal Announcements, 1974-1975 (Box 33:, Folder 412)
    - Book and Journal Announcements, 1976-1978 (Box 34:, Folder 413)
    - Book and Journal Announcements, 1979-1989 (Box 34:, Folder 414)
    - Boston, Gay Groups and Events, 1974-1991 (Box 34:, Folder 415)
    - Articles Pertaining to Anita Bryant, 1977 (Box 34:, Folder 416)
    - Articles Pertaining to Anita Bryant, 1978-1979 (Box 34:, Folder 417)
    - Canada, Gay Organizations and Events, 1970-1985 (Box 34:, Folder 418)
    - Church, Articles and Brochures, 1979-1989 (Box 34:, Folder 419)
    - Church, Articles and Brochures, 1971 (Box 34:, Folder 420)
    - Church, Articles and Brochures, 1972-1985 (Box 34:, Folder 421)
    - Conferences, Fliers, 1970-1993 (Box 35:, Folder 422)
    - Connecticut, Gay Organizations and Events, Fliers, 1968-1986 (Box 35:, Folder 423)
    - Connecticut, Gay Organizations and Events, Fliers, 1987-1999 (Box 35:, Folder 424)
    - The Gay Militants, Publication Announcements, 1971 (Box 35:, Folder 425)
    - Inman, Richard, Typed Manuscript by Richard Inman, 1966 (Box 35:, Folder 426)
    - Judaism, 1974-1977 (Box 35:, Folder 427)
    - Kameny, Franklin, Articles and Typed Manuscripts by Franklin Kameny, 1963-1975 (Box 35:, Folder 428)
    - Lesbian, Organizations and Events, 1967-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 429)
    - Lesbian ,Organizations and Events, 1975-1980 (Box 35:, Folder 430)
    - Lesbian, Organizations and Events, 1982-1985 (Box 35:, Folder 431)
    - Lesbian,O rganizations and Events, 1986-1988 (Box 35:, Folder 432)
    - Los Angeles, 1966-1969 (Box 35:, Folder 433)
    - Marches and Conferences, Fliers, 1975-1976 (Box 35:, Folder 434)
    - Martin, Bob, News clippings about Bob Martin, 1972-1978 (Box 36:, Folder 435)
    - Martin, Bob, Typed Manuscript by Bob Martin, undated (Box 36:, Folder 436)
    - Martin, Bob, Typed Manuscript by Bob Martin, 1967-1978 (Box 36:, Folder 437)
    - Media, Film, Photography, Radio, Television, 1966-1974 (Box 36:, Folder 438)
    - Merchandise, 1974-1982 (Box 36:, Folder 439)
    - Pearlstein, Sandra, Typed Manuscript by Sandra Pearlstein, 1967 (Box 36:, Folder 440)
    - Political Activism, Organizations and Events, 1968-1971 (Box 36:, Folder 441)
    - Political Activism, Organizations and Events, 1972-1977 (Box 36:, Folder 442)
    - Political Activism, Organizations and Events, 1978-1986 (Box 36:, Folder 443)
    - Pride Week and Marches, 1970-1986 (Box 37:, Folder 449)
    - Pride Week and Marches, 1987-1989 (Box 37:, Folder 450)
    - Psychology, Articles, 1950, 1955, 1964 (Box 37:, Folder 451)
    - Psychology, Articles, 1965 (Box 37:, Folder 452)
    - Psychology, Articles, 1966 (Box 38:, Folder 453)
    - Psychology, Articles, 1966 (Box 38:, Folder 454)
    - Psychology, Articles, 1966 (Box 38:, Folder 455)
    - Psychology, Articles, 1966 (Box 38:, Folder 456)
    - Psychology, Articles, 1967 (Box 38:, Folder 457)
    - Psychology, Articles, 1967-1968 (Box 38:, Folder 458)
    - Psychology, Articles, 1969 (Box 38:, Folder 459)
    - Psychology, Articles, 1969 (Box 38:, Folder 460)
    - Psychology, Articles, 1970, 1971, 1974, 1977, 1982 (Box 39:, Folder 461)
    - The Same Sex Book Review, 1969-1977 (Box 39:, Folder 462)
    - San Francisco, Gay Organizations and Events, 1959-1985 (Box 39:, Folder 463)
    - Invitation from Saul Segal, 1968 (Box 39:, Folder 464)
    - Socialism, 1973-1975 (Box 39:, Folder 466)
    - Solanas, Valerie, Typed Manuscript of "Scum Manifesto", 1967-1968 (Box 39:, Folder 467)
    - Stonewall-Seattle, 1971-1976 (Box 39:, Folder 468)
    - Studd, Gerry, Campaign Promotion, 1984-1986 (Box 39:, Folder 469)
    - Theater, 1967-1979 (Box 39:, Folder 470)
    - Transsexualism and Transvestism, 1969-1982 (Box 39:, Folder 471)
    - Travel, Brochures to Vacation Destinations, 1977-1979 (Box 40:, Folder 472)
    - Travel, Brochures to Vacation Destinations, 1981-1987 (Box 40:, Folder 473)
    - Tri-City National Defense Fund, 1978 (Box 40:, Folder 474)
    - Warner, Arthur C., Unidentified typed manuscript, 1969 (Box 40:, Folder 475)
    - Wood, Robert W. Typed manuscripts, "The Church of the Homosexual" and "Criticism: Christ and the Homosexual", 1966 (Box 40:, Folder 476)
    - Youth Groups, 1969-1975 (Box 40:, Folder 477)
    - Newsclippings
    - Homosexuality, 1959 May - 1966 June (Box 40:, Folder 478)
    - Homosexuality, 1966 July - December (Box 40:, Folder 479)
    - Homosexuality, 1967 (Box 40:, Folder 480)
    - Homosexuality, 1968 (Box 40:, Folder 481)
    - Homosexuality, 1969 (Box 41:, Folder 482)
    - Homosexuality, 1970 January - May (Box 41:, Folder 483)
    - Homosexuality, 1970 June - August (Box 41:, Folder 484)
    - Homosexuality, 1970 September - December (Box 41:, Folder 485)
    - Homosexuality, 1971 January - May (Box 41:, Folder 486)
    - Homosexuality, 1971 June - September (Box 41:, Folder 487)
    - Homosexuality, 1971 October - December (Box 41:, Folder 488)
    - Homosexuality, 1972 January - June (Box 42:, Folder 489)
    - Homosexuality, 1972 July - September (Box 42:, Folder 490)
    - Homosexuality, 1972 October - 1974 December (Box 42:, Folder 491)
    - Homosexuality, 1975 January - 1977 March (Box 42:, Folder 492)
    - Homosexuality, 1977 April - June (Box 42:, Folder 493)
    - Homosexuality, 1977 July - September (Box 42:, Folder 494)
    - Homosexuality, 1977 October - Deember (Box 43:, Folder 495)
    - Homosexuality, 1978 January - May (Box 43:, Folder 496)
    - Homosexuality, 1978 June - October (Box 43:, Folder 497)